#### A PHP Error was encountered

Severity: Warning

Message: mysqli::real\_connect(): (08004/1040): Too many connections

Filename: mysqli/mysqli\_driver.php

Line Number: 202

Backtrace:

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/third\_party/MX/Loader.php  
Line: 107  
Function: DB

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/core/Main\_Controller.php  
Line: 50  
Function: database

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/modules/blog/controllers/Blog.php  
Line: 7  
Function: \_\_construct

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/third\_party/MX/Modules.php  
Line: 112  
Function: \_\_construct

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/libraries/Pc\_hooks.php  
Line: 13  
Function: load

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/core/Main\_Controller.php  
Line: 89  
Function: apply

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/modules/welcome/controllers/Welcome.php  
Line: 26  
Function: \_\_construct

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/index.php  
Line: 298  
Function: require\_once

#### A PHP Error was encountered

Severity: Warning

Message: mysqli::real\_connect(): (08004/1040): Too many connections

Filename: mysqli/mysqli\_driver.php

Line Number: 202

Backtrace:

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/third\_party/MX/Loader.php  
Line: 107  
Function: DB

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/core/My\_Model.php  
Line: 18  
Function: database

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/modules/blog/models/Category\_m.php  
Line: 12  
Function: \_\_construct

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/third\_party/MX/Loader.php  
Line: 228  
Function: \_\_construct

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/modules/blog/models/Blog\_m.php  
Line: 16  
Function: model

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/third\_party/MX/Loader.php  
Line: 228  
Function: \_\_construct

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/modules/blog/controllers/Blog.php  
Line: 8  
Function: model

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/third\_party/MX/Modules.php  
Line: 112  
Function: \_\_construct

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/libraries/Pc\_hooks.php  
Line: 13  
Function: load

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/core/Main\_Controller.php  
Line: 89  
Function: apply

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/modules/welcome/controllers/Welcome.php  
Line: 26  
Function: \_\_construct

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/index.php  
Line: 298  
Function: require\_once

#### A PHP Error was encountered

Severity: Warning

Message: mysqli::real\_connect(): (08004/1040): Too many connections

Filename: mysqli/mysqli\_driver.php

Line Number: 202

Backtrace:

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/third\_party/MX/Loader.php  
Line: 107  
Function: DB

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/core/My\_Model.php  
Line: 18  
Function: database

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/modules/blog/models/Sponsors\_m.php  
Line: 15  
Function: \_\_construct

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/third\_party/MX/Loader.php  
Line: 228  
Function: \_\_construct

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/modules/blog/controllers/Blog.php  
Line: 9  
Function: model

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/third\_party/MX/Modules.php  
Line: 112  
Function: \_\_construct

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/libraries/Pc\_hooks.php  
Line: 13  
Function: load

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/core/Main\_Controller.php  
Line: 89  
Function: apply

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/application/modules/welcome/controllers/Welcome.php  
Line: 26  
Function: \_\_construct

File: /home/bbmedia/domains/iplocation.net/www/index.php  
Line: 298  
Function: require\_once

*    

Privacy Policy
==============

* Privacy Policy

1\. PRIVACY STATEMENT
---------------------

IP Location respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your privacy. Personally identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without your consent. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting any of the sites offered by IP Location, a Brand Media company, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

2\. PERSONAL INFORMATION
------------------------

IP Location collects personal information such as name, address and phone number to provide our services to you. We use your personal information to operate our business, and to deliver services you request. We also use your personal information to inform you of service status as well as products and services available from IP Location.

IP Location does not sell, rent or lease its customer information to third parties. IP Location may access or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, however.

3\. COOKIES
-----------

IP Location uses "cookies" to improve the quality of our service and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies on your web browser. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to use some of our services and features.

4\. MINORS
----------

The protection of children's online privacy is very important to us. IP Location does not sell services for purchase by children. If you are under 13, you may use our services only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

5\. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY
-----------------------------

IP Location may occasionally update this "Privacy Policy" to better meet our business needs. Specifically, this Privacy Policy may be updated to reflect new features, services, and any changes on the use of personal information. Continued use of IP Location website and its services will indicate that you agree with such changes. We encourage you to periodically review our privacy policy to be informed of how we protect your privacy information.

6\. QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS
--------------------------

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at admin@iplocation.net.

### IP Tools

### Domain Tools

### Blog Categories

### About Us

Welcome to IP Location, the home of IP Geolocation, security and privacy resources. This website was built to offer tips, tutorials and articles on IP address, VPN, Proxy, DDoS and WebAuthn technologies.

### Popular Topics

### Company Info

* [Login](https://www.iplocation.net/login) / [Signup](https://www.iplocation.net/register)

### Socialize

Subscribe to our newsletter:

 Subscribe

[](https://www.facebook.com/IPLocation.net/)**Like Us**  
on Facebook

[](https://twitter.com/iplocation_net)**Twitter**  
on Twitter

[](#)**LinkedIn**  
on LinkedIn

[](#)**Instagram**  
on Instagram

##### Do not sell or share my personal information.

×

At IPLocation.net, we prioritize the privacy and security of our visitors. We want you to feel confident and comfortable when browsing our website. That's why we want to assure you that we do not sell or share any personal information collected from our website.  
  
Your trust is important to us. Whether you're browsing our site for information, or engaging with our content, rest assured that any data you provide remains strictly confidential. We adhere to stringent privacy policies and comply with all relevant regulations to safeguard your information.  
  
Your privacy matters, and we are committed to maintaining the highest standards of data protection. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy practices, please don't hesitate to reach out to us.

OK

© 2006 - 2024, Brand Media, Inc. All rights reserved.
